John Cohen collection, circa 1939-2019
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Sound recordings and moving images, ca. 1950-2010
  - Subseries 2. Huayno disc collection, ca. 1960-1990
    - Andino H-063, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR241; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Artidoro Huerta y su Guitarra
    - Andino H-062, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR242; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Volcan 101, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR243; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Soledad Puro Corazon y Antonio Gutierrez Cateriano
    - Santiango 016, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR244; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto Nativo
    - Spo. 7 [San Pedro], undated, AFC 2011/059: SR245; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Huayno; Motivo Costumbrista
    - Andino H-061, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR246; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Pichuichancas de Tauya
    - Andino H-059, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR248; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-058, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR249; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Jilgueros de Pachangara
    - Andino H-054, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR250; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Franternal Sumbilca de Canta
    - Andino H-088, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR251; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Hermanos Samar
    - Andino H-083, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR252; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Mensajeros de los Andes
    - Andino H-081, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR253; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Carmen Alto de Ayacucho
    - Andino H-068, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR254; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Grauinos
    - Andino H-066, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR255; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-116 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR256, SR257; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      La Sihuasinita y su Conjunto
    - Andino H-105, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR258; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Bohemios de Puquio
    - Andino H-096, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR259; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Querubines
    - Andino H-095, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR260; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Solteritos
    - Andino H-089, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR261; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-151, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR262; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Centro Musical Huasta
    - Andino H-148, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR263; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orquesta Aurora Andina
    - Andino H-142, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR264; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      El Fuego de tu Mirada
    - Andino H-141, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR265; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto Musical Coris
    - Andino H-145, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR266; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Autenticos de Obas
    - Andino H-138, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR267; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Alfonso Fabian y su Arpa
    - Andino H-136, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR268; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto los Laureles de Pomabamba
    - Andino H-134, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR269; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Trio Los Andes Cerrenos
    - Andino H-137, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR270; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-133, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR271; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Duo Winay
    - Andino H-132, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR272; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Pagador
    - Andino H-126, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR273; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Incomparables
    - Andino H-101, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR274; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Amanecer Ancashino
    - Andino H-122, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR275; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Saco Largo
    - Andino H-183, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR276; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Filarmonica Capillas Sur
    - Almeri 086, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR277; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Pachachacas de Cuterva
    - Almersa 013, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR278; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Eugenio Huaroc
    - Andino 003, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR279; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Cedros de Apongo
    - Andino H-156, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR280; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-157, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR281; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-163, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR282; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Nortenos
    - Andino H-164, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR283; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orq. Los Caminantes de Huancayo
    - Andino H-165, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR284; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-169, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR285; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto los Liricos de Puquio
    - Andino H-174, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR286; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Compania los Obreros del Peru
    - Andino H-176, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR287; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. los Hijos del Huascaran
    - Andino H-177, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR288; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-180 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR289, SR290; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Luis Abanto y su Conjunto
    - Andino H-183, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR291; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Qori Llajta de Capillas Sur; Banda Filarmonica Capillas Sur
    - Andino H-189 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR292, SR293; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Trio los Crucenos de Puquio
    - Andino H-190, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR294; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-194, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR295; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Vernacular Aguilas de Cerro de Pasco
    - Andino H-199, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR296; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino H-200, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR297; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Solteritos del Centro
    - Andino H-210 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR298, SR299; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Senor de los Milagros de Carampoma
    - Andino H-211, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR300; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Fernando Pineda y los Andinos de Caujul
    - Andino 3348, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR301; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Irma Medina; Carmencita Chalco y su Conjunto
    - Andino 5521, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR302; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Melodias del Ande
    - Andino 5524, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR303; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Huayanitos de Rampon
    - Andino 5525, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR304; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Idolos de Jauja
    - Andino 5527, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR305; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Senor de los Milagros
    - Andino 5528 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR306, SR307; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      La Calandria de Huancayo y su Orq. Folklorica
    - Andino 5532, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR308; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino 5533, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR309; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orquesta los Embajadores de Tarma
    - Andino 5538, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR310; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Halcones de Pacchu
    - Andino 5545 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR311, SR312; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Musical Sol Andino Huanja-Huaraz
    - Andino 5549, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR313; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. San Agustin de Punun
    - Andino 5555, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR314; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Marcelino Quispe y su Arpa
    - Andino 5556, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR315; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Estudiantina Cuerdas del Lago
    - Andino 5557, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR316; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conh. Musical Coris
    - Andino 5558, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR317; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino 5560, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR318; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Peregrina del Norte y el Conj. Sol de los Andes
    - Andino 5565, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR319; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Filarmonica Saavedra de Anchucaya
    - Andino 5573 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR320, SR321; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Gorrioncitos de Jucul
    - Andino 5574, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR322; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Melodias de Tarma
    - Andino 5575 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR323, SR324; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Julio y Sus Mateitos
    - Andino 5579, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR325; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Santo Domingo de Laraos
    - Andino 5582, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR326; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Centro Musical Ayaranga
    - Andino 5585, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR327; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Andino 5586, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR328; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Huayanitos de Ranpon
    - Andino 5591, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR329; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cojunto Melodias del Ande
    - Andino 5592 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR330, SR331; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Alejandro Sanchez Conjunto Ases de Cascay
    - Andino 5594, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR332; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cholita del Huascaran y su Conjunto
    - Apurimac 0015, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR333; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Tulio Sevillano; H. Rodrigues
    - Apurimac 13104, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR334; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      El Solitario de Cajacay y su Conjunto
    - Arriba Peru, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR335; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. "Los Zorzales de Santa Cruz"
    - Chasqui 006, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR336; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Olimpicos de Huancayo
    - Chasqui 009, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR337; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Ayarichi Estrella de Puno
    - Chasqui 010, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR338; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Panchito Leytth y su Violin
    - Chasqui 016, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR339; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Jumpy Mayuck
    - Chasqui 021, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR340; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orq. Juventud Lira Huancaina
    - Chasqui 023, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR341; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Estudiantina Andamarca
    - Chasqui 029, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR342; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. "Los Mensajeros de Surcubamba"
    - Chasqui 033, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR343; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      "Conjunto Expresion Yauyina"
    - Chasqui 034, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR344; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Interandino del Peru
    - Chasqui 053, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR345; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Centro Musical Vilcabamba
    - Chasqui 066, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR346; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Caporales de Pauran
    - Chasqui 085, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR347; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto Zamponas de Camilaca
    - Chasqui 087, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR348; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Centro Union Choquelihue-Puno
    - Chasqui 088, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR349; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Luceros de Huancavelica
    - Chasqui 091, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR350; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Nahuischa
    - Chasqui 103 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR351, SR352; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Apu Inca de Pomabamba
    - Chaqui 105, version 1, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR353; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Mensajeros de Salcabamba
    - Chaqui 105, version 2, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR354; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Artemio Medina y su Conjunto
    - Chasqui 106, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR355; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Chiquita Alisinita
    - Chasqui 107, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR356; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Juanita del Rosal y la Bda. Los Aguiluchos de Puquio
    - Chasqui 108, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR357; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Chasqui 109 (2 copies) undated, AFC 2011/059: SR358, SR359; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      BDA. Micaela Bastidas de Apurimac
    - Chasqui 111, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR361; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Mensajeros de Cajatambo
    - Chasqui 113, copy 1, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR362; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Las Pastoras de Palmayo; Conj. Los Comuneros de Palmayo
    - Chasqui 113, copy 2, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR363; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Chasqui 122, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR364; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Miniponchos
    - Chasqui 123, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR365; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Hnos. Jimenez
    - Chasqui 131, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR366; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Tarkeadas
    - Chasqui 137, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR367; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orquesta Tipica "San Pedro de Pilas" (Yauyos)
    - Chasqui 144, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR368; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Chasqui 152, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR369; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto Derrepente
    - Chasqui 153, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR370; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Chasqui 324, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR371; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Estrellas de Lucanamarca
    - Chasqui 391, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR372; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Hermanos Yaranga
    - Chasqui 392, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR373; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Viajeros de Pazos
    - Chasqui 439, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR374; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Ecos de Tinca
    - Chasqui 488 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR375, SR376; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      El Solitario de San Antonio de Puquio y su Arpa
    - Cholita Record 001, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR377; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Libertadores de Pueblo Libre Conjunto de Shacshas Cholita del Huascaran
    - Corona 5069 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR378, SR379; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Banda Los Pillco Mozos de Huanuco
    - Cumbe 014, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR380; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Atahualpa; Conj. Aires de Porcon
    - Diasa 04394, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR381; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Hnos Huayhuas de Umamarca
    - Diasa 13104, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR382; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Sofia Guerrero y su Conjunto
    - DIFA 004, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR383; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      "Los Mensajeros " (De Canete)
    - DIPSA 1267, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR384; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Marciano Torres y su Arpa Voladora
    - Edihna 16288, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR385; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      "Los Jigueros de Huando"
    - Elchancayano 017, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR386; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Mina Gonzales y Totito de Santa Cruz
    - Estrella Records ER-05, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR387; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Esther Suares y su Arpa
    - Estrella Records ER-112, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR388; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Agrupacion Musical Coaza
    - Estrella Records 125, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR389; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Torito Pintado, Simon Medrano y su Violin
    - Estrella Records 139, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR390; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Ccorihua Yllas y Las Golondrinas de Acoria
    - FAMA 004, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR391; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto Juventud Hualgayoc
    - Hualaycho 009, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR392; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Juventud Nuevo Amanecer de: Occobamba-Marangani
    - Hualaycho 012, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR393; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Huerfanitos de Cconamuro
    - IFESMA, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR394; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Pasionaria de los Andes y su Orquesta
    - Imaca 04394, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR395; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunta Nube Blanca
    - Imsa Records 001, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR396; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Shiringueros
    - Imsa Records 026, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR397; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Selva Alegre
    - Industria Alefelsa Peruana 0050, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR398; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Los Manantiales de Pampa Cangallo
    - IEMPSA/Lider 04.06.64, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR399; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Nelly Munguia
    - IEMPSA/Lider 04.06.71, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR400; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      "Bailemos Santiago" Con Panchito Leyth
    - IEMPSA/Lider 11821, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR401; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Condemayta de Acomayo
    - IEMPSA/Lider 21.15.1969, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR402; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Pepe Vasquez
    - Juivillano 04394, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR403; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Maria Sanches y su Conj. Lucero Ambarino
    - Macho Diaz, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR404; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Radiantes de Santa Ana de Huaycahuacho
    - Machu Picchu 2029, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR405; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cholo Andino y su Sandurria; Jose Corrales y su Bandurrias
    - Machu Picchu 2086, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR406; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cuarteto Folklorico Andino
    - Mag 2328, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR407; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Romanceros de Marco
    - Mag 2575, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR408; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Idolos de Centro
    - Mag 2992, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR409; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Orq. Tipica Aramachay de Jauja
    - Mag 3350, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR410; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Fiesta Peruana
    - Manturano 155, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR411; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      La Ocobambinita y su Conjunto
    - Manturano 156, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR412; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Mensajeros de Pampachiri
    - Maribel 0019, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR413; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Realz: Luis Severo Damian
    - Maribel 0020, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR414; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Maribel 059, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR415; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Catalina Farfan
    - Odeon 45-029, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR416; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Zorzales Jaujinos
    - Odeon 45-8788, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR417; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Caraybamba
    - Odeon 45-8845, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR418; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Lira Paucina
    - Odeon 45-8953, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR419; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Errantes y sus Guitarras
    - Odeon 10387, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR420; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      La Huarancinita con el Conj. Rondalla Ancashina
    - Ollanta 03, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR421; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      San Marcos de Rocchac
    - Ollanta 013, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR422; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Luceros de Sumbilca
    - Ollanta 033, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR423; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Flor de Acomayo y su Conjunto
    - Ollanta 050, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR424; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Quendes de Cajabamba
    - Ollanta 070, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR425; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Corazon de San Marcos
    - Ollanta 110, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR426; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Rosa de Larmenta Peregrinos de Larmenta
    - Ollanta 169, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR427; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Violeta Valdez, Atahualpa de Cajamarca
    - Ollanta 172, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR428; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      San Marcos de Bocchacc
    - Ollanta 312, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR429; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Hijos de Huancaraylla
    - Ollanta 359, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR430; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Pascuala, Jacy, Della Cabrera
    - Ollanta 381, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR431; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      El Chatito Juve y Chino Pedro Luceros de Sumbilca
    - Otridisa, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR432; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Los Carnavaleros
    - Quipas, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR433; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto: "Estudiantina Colca." Cantan: Las Hijas de Colca.
    - Peru Canta, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR434; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Agrupacion Folklorica Huaycahuacho
    - Philips 6046045, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR435; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Picaflor de los Andes y su Orquesta
    - Plateado 20, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR436; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. San Edilfonzo de Tauripampa
    - Plateado 24, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR437; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj. Mensajeros del Canipaco
    - Plateado 33, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR438; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Jesus Tumi
    - Plateado 39, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR439; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Virgen Asuncion de Apomgo
    - Primicas 10-8509, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR440; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Anita Lucia Proano
    - Discos Prodisar 130, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR441; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto los Aires de Sangarara
    - Discos Prodisar 150, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR442; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Wankas
    - Discos Prodisar 1017, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR443; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Los Jaraneros de Canas
    - Discos del Puerto 102, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR444; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Nuevo Corazon de Sumac Marca
    - Discos del Puerto 105, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR445; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Nuevo Corazon de Sumac Marca de Marangani
    - Discos del Puerto 117, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR446; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Linda Huanchurina, Banda Musical Filarmonica Acopampa
    - Discos del Puerto 125, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR447; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cori Jalhuacha
    - Discos del Puerto 126, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR448; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Los Engreidos de San Mateo
    - Discos del Puerto 132, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR449; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Hermanos Milla
    - Discos del Puerto 138 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR450, SR451; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conjunto los Aventureros de Choqquetira
    - Discos del Puerto 140, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR452; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Las Pallas de Pachabamba y Marcial Carhuamaca
    - Discos del Puerto 144, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR453; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Florcita Salkantay; Conj.: Brisas de Lamay
    - Discos del Puerto 173, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR454; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: La Campesinita de Acomayo
    - Discos del Puerto 177, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR455; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Cantan: Azucenita del Sur y Oreganito del Sur
    - Discos del Puerto 186, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR456; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Ruben Dolores y su Arpa Jaranista
    - Discos del Puerto 189, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR457; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Lo Mejor del Centro; Varios Interpretes
    - Discos del Puerto 199, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR458; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Jorge Bravo; Conj.: Los Mensajeros de Uchupata
    - Discos del Puerto 209, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR459; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Copo Rayada
    - Discos del Puerto 211, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR460; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Los Olimpicos de Aurelio Miranda. Canta: Juanita del Rosal
    - Discos del Puerto 216, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR461; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Miguel Parra; Conj.: Los Diamantes de Llata
    - Discos del Puerto 217 (2 copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR462, SR463; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Conj.: Los Danzantes de Tijeras; Los Ccahuallactas Ayacucho
    - Discos del Puerto 224, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR488; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: La Uruysinita con el Conj. "Los Danzantes de Puquio"
    - Discos del Puerto 262 (two copies), undated, AFC 2011/059: SR464, SR465; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Florcita de Cabana; Conj.: Danzantes de Tijeras los Ccahuallactas
    - Discos del Puerto 263, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR466; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
    - Discos del Puerto 278, undated, AFC 2011/059: SR467; 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in.
      Canta: Juana Lidia Argumedo y su Conjunto